Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Observations of New Variables, 1906-10-18/1907-06-06; phaedra0949 (Box 37)
  KG11365.948
- Observations of New Variables, 1907-02-20/1914-12-04; phaedra0950 (Box 37)
  KG11365.949
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes - T plates, 1907-11-21/1909-03-11; phaedra0951 (Box 37)
  KG11365.950
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes, 1908-11-03/1910-07-25; phaedra0952 (Box 37)
  KG11365.951
- Standard Magnitudes, 1909-05-04/1914-03-15; phaedra0953 (Box 37)
  KG11365.952
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes - South Pole, 1910-07-07/1917-01-12; phaedra0954 (Box 37)
  KG11365.953
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes, 1910-07-26/1911-01-13; phaedra0955 (Box 37)
  KG11365.954
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes, 1911-01-14/1914-10-22; phaedra0956 (Box 37)
  KG11365.955
- Miscellaneous Journal, 1911-06-01/1912-05-04; phaedra0957 (Box 37)
  KG11365.956
- Miscellaneous, 1912-05-03/1914-12-01; phaedra0958 (Box 37)
  KG11365.957
- Objects looked up by request, 1914-06-13/1918-05-06; phaedra0959 (Box 37)
  KG11365.958
- Standard Magnitudes, 1914-11-07/1919-02-12; phaedra0960 (Box 37)
  KG11365.959
- Miscellaneous - Comp. Stars, 1914-12-01/1916-08-05; phaedra0961 (Box 37)
  KG11365.960
  37
- Catalogs Comparison Stars, 1915-06-26/1919-04-02; phaedra0962 (Box 37)
  KG11365.961
  38
- Miscellaneous (Variables), 1915-10-20/1919-11-18; phaedra0963 (Box 37)
  KG11365.962
- Discovery of New Variables, 1916-01-22/1920-07-26; phaedra0964 (Box 37)
  KG11365.963
- Miscellaneous (esp. Novae), 1916-06-06/1920-01-19; phaedra0965 (Box 37)
  KG11365.964
- Standard Magnitudes, 1919-07-30/1921-06-21; phaedra0966 (Box 37)
  KG11365.965
  43
- Miscellaneous (Variables), 1920/1921; phaedra0967 (Box 37)
  KG11365.966
  44
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables, 1893/1896; phaedra0968 (Box 37)
  KG11365.967
  Evelyn F. Leland
  1893phae.proj..968L
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896; phaedra0969 (Box 38)
  KG11365.968
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896; phaedra0970 (Box 38)
  KG11365.969
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896/1897; phaedra0971 (Box 38)
  KG11365.970
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1897/1898; phaedra0972 (Box 38)
  KG11365.971
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables W Cen., 1897/1898; phaedra0973 (Box 38)
  KG11365.972
- Measure of Eros (South Pole), 1899/1902; phaedra0974 (Box 38)
  KG11365.973
- Measures, new satellite (Phoebe) of Saturn, Nova Sgr, 1899/1906; phaedra0975 (Box 38)
  KG11365.974
- Measures of M3, etc., 1902/1903; phaedra0976 (Box 38)
  KG11365.975
- Measures of Eros, 1902/1904; phaedra0977 (Box 38)
  KG11365.976
- Search for variables; measures, 1902/1903; phaedra0978 (Box 38)
  KG11365.977
- Search for variables; measures, 1903/1904; phaedra0979 (Box 38)
  KG11365.978
- Search for variables; measures, 1904/1907; phaedra0980 (Box 38)
  KG11365.979
- Search for variables; measures, 1907/1909; phaedra0981 (Box 38)
  KG11365.980
  31 or 32
- Search for variables; measures, 1904/1910; phaedra0982 (Box 38)
  KG11365.981
- Scale measures, 1907/1910; phaedra0983 (Box 38)
  KG11365.982
- Scale measures, 1911/1912; phaedra0984 (Box 38)
  KG11365.983
- Scale measures, 1910/1912; phaedra0985 (Box 38)
  KG11365.984
- Scale measures, 1910/1911; phaedra0986 (Box 38)
  KG11365.985
- Scale measures, 1912; phaedra0987 (Box 38)
  KG11365.986
- Scale measures, 1913/1914; phaedra0988 (Box 38)
  KG11365.987
- Series Reductions, 1913; phaedra0989 (Box 39)
  KG11365.988
- Observing Book - M5, 1913; phaedra0990 (Box 39)
  KG11365.989
- Series Reductions, 1913; phaedra0991 (Box 39)
  KG11365.990
- Series Reductions, 1913/1914; phaedra0992 (Box 39)
  KG11365.991
- Series Reductions and M5 variables, 1914/1915; phaedra0993 (Box 39)
  KG11365.992
- Series Reductions, 1913/1914; phaedra0994 (Box 39)
  KG11365.993
- Series Reductions, 1913/1915; phaedra0995 (Box 39)
  KG11365.994
  46
- Series Reductions, 1914/1915; phaedra0996 (Box 39)
  KG11365.995
  47
- Series Reductions, 1914/1915; phaedra0997 (Box 39)
  KG11365.996
  48
- Series Reductions, 1915/1917; phaedra0998 (Box 39)
  KG11365.997
- Series Reductions, 1915/1917; phaedra0999 (Box 39)
  KG11365.998
- Series Reductions, 1915/1917; phaedra1000 (Box 39)
  KG11365.999
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917; phaedra1001 (Box 39)
  KG11366.000
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1916/1917; phaedra1002 (Box 39)
  KG11366.001
  52
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917/1918; phaedra1003 (Box 39)
  KG11366.002
  54
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917/1918; phaedra1004 (Box 39)
  KG11366.003
  55
- Observing Book, 1918; phaedra1005 (Box 39)
  KG11366.004
- Observing Book, 1918; phaedra1006 (Box 39)
  KG11366.005
- Long Exposure H.S. Regions and Series, 1918/1919; phaedra1007 (Box 39)
  KG11366.006
- New Satellite of Saturn and North Polar Sequence, 1904/1911; phaedra1008 (Box 39)
  KG11366.007
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1918/1919; phaedra1009 (Box 40)
  KG11366.008
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919; phaedra1010 (Box 40)
  KG11366.009
  60
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919/1920; phaedra1011 (Box 40)
  KG11366.010
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919/1920; phaedra1012 (Box 40)
  KG11366.011
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1920; phaedra1013 (Box 40)
  KG11366.012
- MF Series, 1920; phaedra1014 (Box 40)
  KG11366.013
- MF Series, 1920/1921; phaedra1015 (Box 40)
  KG11366.014
- MC and A Plates, 1921; phaedra1016 (Box 40)
  KG11366.015
  66
- Large Magellanic Cloud, 1921; phaedra1017 (Box 40)
  KG11366.016
- MC Plates, 1921/1922; phaedra1018 (Box 40)
  KG11366.017
- MC Plates, 1915/1916; phaedra1019 (Box 40)
  KG11366.018
  H.S. Locke
- MC Plates, 1915/1916; phaedra1020 (Box 40)
  KG11366.019
- MC Plates, 1916; phaedra1021 (Box 40)
  KG11366.020
- MC Plates, 1916/1918; phaedra1022 (Box 40)
  KG11366.021
- MC Plates, 1916/1917; phaedra1023 (Box 40)
  KG11366.022
- MC Plates, 1917; phaedra1024 (Box 40)
  KG11366.023
- Miscellaneous Plates, 1917/1918; phaedra1025 (Box 40)
  KG11366.024
- MC Plates, 1917/1918; phaedra1026 (Box 40)
  KG11366.025
- MC Plates, 1917/1918; phaedra1027 (Box 40)
  KG11366.026
- B and MC Plates, 1917/1919; phaedra1028 (Box 40)
  KG11366.027
- Observing Book, 1910/1919; phaedra1029 (Box 41)
  KG11366.028
  Johanna C.S. Mackie
- Observing Book (Scale Measures), 1913/1918; phaedra1030 (Box 41)
  KG11366.029
- Observing Book (MD Plates), 1913/1919; phaedra1031 (Box 41)
  KG11366.030
- Observing Book (Miscllaneous Plates), 1918/1919; phaedra1032 (Box 41)
  KG11366.031
- B Series, 1919; phaedra1033 (Box 41)
  KG11366.032
- Observing Book (B Series), 1919; phaedra1034 (Box 41)
  KG11366.033
- Observing Book (Miscellaneous Measures), 1919/1920; phaedra1035 (Box 41)
  KG11366.034
  M.K.
- Novae(Maps of S, AC Plates), 1919/1920; phaedra1036 (Box 41)
  KG11366.035
  Title uncertain
- Observing Book - Variable Stars, 1912/1913; phaedra1037 (Box 41)
  KG11366.036
- Observing Book - Scale Measures, 1913; phaedra1038 (Box 41)
  KG11366.037
- Observing Book Series Measures, 1913/1916; phaedra1039 (Box 41)
  KG11366.038
- Observing Book - Series, etc., 1914; phaedra1040 (Box 41)
  KG11366.039
- Observing Book Miscellaneous, 1914/1915; phaedra1041 (Box 41)
  KG11366.040
- Circumpolar variables, 1914/1915; phaedra1042 (Box 41)
  KG11366.041
- Circumpolar variables, 1914/1915; phaedra1043 (Box 41)
  KG11366.042
- Series Measures (principally blue plates), 1915; phaedra1044 (Box 41)
  KG11366.043
- Series Measures (principally yellow plates), 1915/1916; phaedra1045 (Box 41)
  KG11366.044
- Circumpolar variables, 1914/1916; phaedra1046 (Box 41)
  KG11366.045
- Circumpolar variables (estimate of brightness), 1915/1916; phaedra1047 (Box 41)
  KG11366.046
- Circumpolar variables (overflow), 1915; phaedra1048 (Box 41)
  KG11366.047
- Circumpolar variables, 1916; phaedra1049 (Box 42)
  KG11366.048
- Circumpolar variables (record of observations on photographs), 1916; phaedra1050 (Box 42)
  KG11366.049
- Tables of Ursae Majoris, 1894/1896; phaedra1051 (Box 42)
  KG11366.050
  Antonia C. Maury
- Rotation of Primary Star and Separation of Satellites, 1928/1932; phaedra1052 (Box 42)
  KG11366.051
- Formulae for reduction, Phase in HA84, 1918/1922; phaedra1053 (Box 42)
  KG11366.052
- Beta Lyras and others (loose papers), 1933; phaedra1054 (Box 42)
  KG11366.053
- Observation Book, Measurement of Variables and Standard Sequence, 1912; phaedra1055 (Box 42)
  KG11366.054
  Mollie E. O'Reilly
- Miscellaneous Observations, Variables, Etc., 1914/1917; phaedra1056 (Box 42)
  KG11366.055
- Scale Measurements of Standard Regions on I series, 1913/1914; phaedra1057 (Box 42)
  KG11366.056
- Circumpolar variables - measurements of comp stars, 1914; phaedra1058 (Box 42)
  KG11366.057
- MC Plates, 1914; phaedra1059 (Box 42)
  KG11366.058
- Measurements of Miscellaneous Plates, 1914; phaedra1060 (Box 42)
  KG11366.059
- Measurements of Miscellaneous Plates, 1914; phaedra1061 (Box 42)
  KG11366.060
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914; phaedra1062 (Box 42)
  KG11366.061
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914; phaedra1063 (Box 42)
  KG11366.062
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914/1915; phaedra1064 (Box 42)
  KG11366.063
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914/1915; phaedra1065 (Box 42)
  KG11366.064
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915/1917; phaedra1066 (Box 42)
  KG11366.065
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; phaedra1067 (Box 42)
  KG11366.066
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; phaedra1068 (Box 42)
  KG11366.067
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; phaedra1069 (Box 43)
  KG11366.068
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; phaedra1070 (Box 43)
  KG11366.069
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915/1916; phaedra1071 (Box 43)
  KG11366.070
- Southern and AS Plates, 1915/1916; phaedra1072 (Box 43)
  KG11366.071
- MC and Misc Plates, 1916/1917; phaedra1073 (Box 43)
  KG11366.072
- Miscellaneous, 1916/1917; phaedra1074 (Box 43)
  KG11366.073
- Obseravtion Book, 1916/1917; phaedra1075 (Box 43)
  KG11366.074
- Southern plates, 1916; phaedra1076 (Box 43)
  KG11366.075
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1916; phaedra1077 (Box 43)
  KG11366.076
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1916/1917; phaedra1078 (Box 43)
  KG11366.077
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1917; phaedra1079 (Box 43)
  KG11366.078
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1917; phaedra1080 (Box 43)
  KG11366.079
- Miscellaneous, 1917/1918; phaedra1081 (Box 43)
  KG11366.080
- Miscellaneous, 1917/1918; phaedra1082 (Box 43)
  KG11366.081
- Obseravtion Book, 1918; phaedra1083 (Box 43)
  KG11366.082
- Scale measures, 1918; phaedra1084 (Box 43)
  KG11366.083
- B Series, 1918; phaedra1085 (Box 43)
  KG11366.084
- Catalogue of Sc. Measures, 1918; phaedra1086 (Box 43)
  KG11366.085
- For Catalogue, 1 degree Square, 1918; phaedra1087 (Box 43)
  KG11366.086
- Cat 4 degree Square, 1918; phaedra1088 (Box 43)
  KG11366.087
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial, 1910-11-30/1912-03-22; phaedra1089 (Box 44)
  KG11366.088
  Philip G. O'Reilly
  1910phae.proj.1089O
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial, 1912-03-22/1913-01-28; phaedra1090 (Box 44)
  KG11366.089
  1912phae.proj.1090O
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial (variables), 1913-01-28/1914-01; phaedra1091 (Box 44)
  KG11366.090
  1913phae.proj.1091O
- Various Plate measures, 1924-02; phaedra1092 (Box 44)
  KG11366.091
  Cecilia H. Payne
  1924phae.proj.1092P
  Full-Text Searchable PDF
  phaedra1092 full text
- Various Plate measures, 1924; phaedra1093 (Box 44)
  KG11366.092
  1924phae.proj.1093P
- Various Plate measures, 1924; phaedra1094 (Box 44)
  KG11366.093
  1924phae.proj.1094P
- Various Plate measures, 1925; phaedra1095 (Box 44)
  KG11366.094
  Contributor: Sergei I. Gaposchkin
  Sergei I. Gaposchkin
  1925phae.proj.1095P
  Contains inked sketch labeled "Sergei's Drawing"
- Wavelength Calculations, 1924/1925; phaedra1096 (Box 44)
  KG11366.095
  1924phae.proj.1096P
- Aperture of MC plates, 1924/1929; phaedra1097 (Box 44)
  Approximate date range 1924-1929
  KG11366.096
  1924phae.proj.1097P
- Emission lines, Apertured Spectra, 1924/1929; phaedra1098 (Box 44)
  KG11366.097
  1924phae.proj.1098P
- Apertured Spectra. Measures and Reductions. Arcturus, Vega, 1924/1929; phaedra1099 (Box 44)
  KG11366.098
  1924phae.proj.1099P
- Microphotometer, General, 1924/1929; phaedra1100 (Box 44)
  KG11366.099
  1924phae.proj.1100P
- Apertured and Single Spectra, 1924/1929; phaedra1101 (Box 44)
  KG11366.100
  1924phae.proj.1101P
- Apertured c Stars and Others, 1924/1929; phaedra1102 (Box 44)
  KG11366.101
  1924phae.proj.1102P
- Single Spectra (Capella, Rigel, Sirius, Altair), 1924/1929; phaedra1103 (Box 44)
  KG11366.102
  1924phae.proj.1103P
- Apertured beta Cas, 1924/1929; phaedra1104 (Box 44)
  KG11366.103
  1924phae.proj.1104P
- General Ledgers, 1924/1929; phaedra1105 (Box 44)
  KG11366.104
  1924phae.proj.1105P
- Line Photometry, 1924/1929; phaedra1106 (Box 45)
  KG11366.105
  1924phae.proj.1106P
- Gaertner, 1927; phaedra1107 (Box 45)
  KG11366.106
  1927phae.proj.1107P
- Line Photometry, 1924/1929; phaedra1108 (Box 45)
  KG11366.107
  1924phae.proj.1108P
- Plates, 1926; phaedra1109 (Box 45)
  KG11366.108
  1926phae.proj.1109P
- Line Photometery: Apertured Mira, alpha Cygnus, alpha Persei, 1924/1929; phaedra1110 (Box 45)
  KG11366.109
  1924phae.proj.1110P
- Pleiades Background, 1924/1929; phaedra1111 (Box 45)
  KG11366.110
  1924phae.proj.1111P
- Line Mira, Zeta UMa Summary, 1924/1929; phaedra1112 (Box 45)
  KG11366.111
  1924phae.proj.1112P
- K Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1113 (Box 45)
  KG11366.112
  1924phae.proj.1113P
- Color Magnitude: Angstrom Magnitudes, 1924/1929; phaedra1114 (Box 45)
  KG11366.113
  1924phae.proj.1114P
- Schilt Microphotometer, 1924/1929; phaedra1115 (Box 45)
  KG11366.114
  1924phae.proj.1115P
- C-Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1116 (Box 45)
  KG11366.115
  1924phae.proj.1116P
- C-Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1117 (Box 45)
  KG11366.116
  1924phae.proj.1117P
- C-Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1118 (Box 45)
  KG11366.117
  1924phae.proj.1118P
- B-Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1119 (Box 45)
  KG11366.118
  1924phae.proj.1119P
- Line Photometry: C-Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1120 (Box 45)
  KG11366.119
  1924phae.proj.1120P
- Temperatures, 1924/1929; phaedra1121 (Box 45)
  KG11366.120
  1924phae.proj.1121P
- Magnitudes, 1924/1929; phaedra1122 (Box 46)
  KG11366.121
  1924phae.proj.1122P
- Line Areas, 1924/1929; phaedra1123 (Box 46)
  KG11366.122
  1924phae.proj.1123P
- Long Dispersion Spectrophotometry, 1924/1929; phaedra1124 (Box 46)
  KG11366.123
  1924phae.proj.1124P
- Line Areas, 1924/1929; phaedra1125 (Box 46)
  KG11366.124
  1924phae.proj.1125P
- K Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1126 (Box 46)
  KG11366.125
  1924phae.proj.1126P
- Line Countours, O Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1127 (Box 46)
  KG11366.126
  1924phae.proj.1127P
- Microphotometry null of C Stars, 1924/1929; phaedra1128 (Box 46)
  KG11366.127
  1924phae.proj.1128P
- Identifications (Sequences), 1924/1929; phaedra1129 (Box 46)
  KG11366.127.1
  1924phae.proj.1129P
- Various Plate measures, 1926/1926; phaedra1130 (Box 46)
  Start date inferred.
  KG11366.128
  Research team head: Cecilia H. Payne
  Research team head:
  Madelen R. Dwyer
  1926phae.proj.1130D
- Various Plate measures, 1926/1926; phaedra1131 (Box 46)
  KG11366.129
  Mary L. Miller
  1926phae.proj.1131M
- Various Plate measures, 1928/1928; phaedra1132 (Box 46)
  KG11366.130
  Helen M. Lewis
  1928phae.proj.1132L
- Various Plate measures, 1926/1926; phaedra1133 (Box 46)
  KG11366.131
  Jenka Mohr
  1926phae.proj.1133M
- Platinum Grating, Cluster Magnitudes, Cepheid Sequences, 1924/1929; phaedra1134 (Box 46)
  KG11366.132
  C. N. Stein
  1924phae.proj.1134S
- Measures by Bond Astronomy Club under C.H. Payne, 1928; phaedra1135 (Box 46)
  KG11366.133
  Cecilia H. Payne, Everett T. King
  1928phae.proj.1135P
- Various Plate measures, 1927/1927; phaedra1136 (Box 46)
  KG11366.134
  1927phae.proj.1136.
- Miscellaneous, 1877; phaedra1137 (Box 46)
  KG11366.135
  1877phae.proj.1137P
- Correspondence, 1892; phaedra1138 (Box 46)
  KG11366.136
  E.E. Barnard
  1892phae.proj.1138B
- Progress of Draper Catalog, 1891; phaedra1139 (Box 46)
  KG11366.137
  1891phae.proj.1139.
- Miscellaneous, 1879/1888; phaedra1140 (Box 46)
  KG11366.138
  1879phae.proj.1140.
- Various Plate measures, 1890; phaedra1141 (Box 46)
  KG11366.139
  Mabel C. Stevens
  1890phae.proj.1141S
- Miscellaneous Counts for Annual Report, 1899-10-01/1907-10-01; phaedra1142 (Box 47)
  KG11366.140
  1899phae.proj.1142P
- Miscellaneous Counts for Annual Report, 1906-10-01/1921-10-01; phaedra1143 (Box 47)
  KG11366.141
  1906phae.proj.1143P
- Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1902-08-28/1912-12-15; phaedra1144 (Box 47)
  KG11366.142
  1902phae.proj.1144P
- Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1888-09-30/1895-05-28; phaedra1145 (Box 47)
  KG11366.143
  1888phae.proj.1145P
  Contains building sketches and expense notes for construction of Astrophotographic Building
- Accident Book, 1905-12-26/1911-03-04; phaedra1146 (Box 47)
  KG11366.144
  Edward C. Pickering, Solon Irving Bailey
  1905phae.proj.1146P
- Notebook, 1909-01-25; phaedra1147 (Box 47)
  KG11366.145
  1909phae.proj.1147B
- Eye Estimate of Stellar Magnitudes - Instructions, 1881; phaedra1148 (Box 47)
  KG11366.146
  1881phae.proj.1148.
- Plates and Observations, 1878-12-31/1879-04-19; phaedra1149 (Box 47)
  KG11366.147
  Edward C. Pickering, Winslow Upton
  1878phae.proj.1149P
- Measure and Miscellaneous, 1879-04-23/1880-01-07; phaedra1150 (Box 47)
  KG11366.148
  1879phae.proj.1150P
- Eyepiece measurements, 1877/1878; phaedra1151 (Box 47)
  KG11366.149
  Frank Waldo, Winslow Upton, Edward C. Pickering, William H. Pickering
  1877phae.proj.1151W
- Financial Record and Optical computations, 1903-10-28/1908-01-22; phaedra1152 (Box 47)
  KG11366.150
  1903phae.proj.1152P
- Eclipse notebook, 1888-05-30/1900-07-26; phaedra1153 (Box 47)
  KG11366.151
  William H. Pickering
  1888phae.proj.1153P
  Contains information on the preparations and expeditions to see the 1888 and 1900 total solar eclipses
- Determinations of parallax by photographic means, 1882-03-30/1886-03-26; phaedra1154 (Box 47)
  KG11366.152
  1882phae.proj.1154P
- Preparations for observing total eclipse, 1886-04-14; phaedra1155 (Box 47)
  KG11366.153
  1886phae.proj.1155P
- Various essays, 1878/1883; phaedra1156 (Box 47)
  KG11366.154
  1878phae.proj.1156P
  Includes summary of inventions
- Various essays, 1877; phaedra1157 (Box 47)
  KG11366.155
  1877phae.proj.1157P
  Contains accounts of Comet of 1858 and Solar Eclipse of 1878, as well as invention notes and philosophical essays
- Variables and Asteroids, 1914-06-25/1919-01-01; phaedra1158 (Box 47)
  KG11366.156
  Susan Raymond
  1914phae.proj.1158R
- Eros series measures, Eunomia scale measures, 1916-05-25/1917-01-30; phaedra1159 (Box 47)
  KG11366.157
  1916phae.proj.1159R
- Circumpolar variables, 1916-06-23/1917-05-29; phaedra1160 (Box 47)
  KG11366.158
  1916phae.proj.1160R
- Asteroids, 1917-03-26/1917-05-23; phaedra1161 (Box 47)
  KG11366.159
  1917phae.proj.1161R
- Asteroids, Miscellany, 1917-05-24/1918-08-16; phaedra1162 (Box 47)
  KG11366.160
  1917phae.proj.1162R
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1875/1876; phaedra1163 (Box 48)
  KG11366.161
- Plates (Nova Aquilae), 1918; phaedra1164 (Box 48)
  KG11366.162
  Arthur R. Sayer
- M- Determinations, 1918; phaedra1165 (Box 48)
  KG11366.163
- Variable Star Observations, 1909/1910; phaedra1166 (Box 48)
  KG11366.164
  L.G. Schultz
- Observations of Nebulae, 1900; phaedra1167 (Box 48)
  KG11366.165
  Delisle Stewart
- Plate Measures, 1923; phaedra1168 (Box 48)
  KG11366.166
  Rufus O. Suter
- Plate Measures, 1927; phaedra1169 (Box 48)
  KG11366.167
- Observations and calculations - Ecographical position, 1897; phaedra1170 (Box 48)
  KG11366.168
  Winslow Upton
- Latitude and Longitude, Arequipa station, 1896; phaedra1171 (Box 48)
  KG11366.169
- Scale measures - series and chart plates, 1917/1918; phaedra1172 (Box 48)
  KG11366.170
  Mary H. Vann
- Observations of Novae, 1917/1918; phaedra1173 (Box 48)
  KG11366.171
- Observations of Novae, 1918; phaedra1174 (Box 48)
  KG11366.172
- Observations of Novae, 1918; phaedra1175 (Box 48)
  KG11366.173
- Double Star measures, 1876; phaedra1176 (Box 48)
  KG11366.174
  Leonard Waldo
- Correspondence, 1896/1897; phaedra1177 (Box 48)
  KG11366.175
- Observations - 6-inch Telescope, 1911/1913; phaedra1178 (Box 48)
  KG11366.176
  Ida E. Woods
- SS Cygni, 1917; phaedra1179 (Box 48)
  KG11366.177
- Instructions, etc., 1915; phaedra1180 (Box 48)
  KG11366.178
- Observations - 6-inch Telescope, 1912/1917; phaedra1181 (Box 48)
  KG11366.179
- Cluster Variables, 1916; phaedra1182 (Box 49)
  KG11366.180
- Cluster Variables, 1917/1918; phaedra1183 (Box 49)
  KG11366.181
- Cluster Variables, 1919/1923; phaedra1184 (Box 49)
  KG11366.182
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1919; phaedra1185 (Box 49)
  KG11366.183
- Objects suspected as Novae, 1919; phaedra1186 (Box 49)
  KG11366.184
- Examination of AM and AC Plates, 1919/1920; phaedra1187 (Box 49)
  KG11366.185
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1920; phaedra1188 (Box 49)
  KG11366.186
- New Variables, 1920/1922; phaedra1189 (Box 49)
  KG11366.187
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920; phaedra1190 (Box 49)
  KG11366.188
- Examination of Northern Regions, 1920; phaedra1191 (Box 49)
  KG11366.189
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920; phaedra1192 (Box 49)
  KG11366.190
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920/1921; phaedra1193 (Box 49)
  KG11366.191
- Objects suspected as Novae, 1921; phaedra1194 (Box 49)
  KG11366.192
- Special Objects, 1922; phaedra1195 (Box 49)
  KG11366.193
- Examination of Southern Regions, 1922; phaedra1196 (Box 49)
  KG11366.194
- New Variables, 1922; phaedra1197 (Box 49)
  KG11366.195
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1922/1923; phaedra1198 (Box 49)
  KG11366.196
- Nebulae and Asteroids, 1923; phaedra1199 (Box 49)
  KG11366.197
- Cluster Variables, 1923; phaedra1200 (Box 49)
  KG11366.198
- Cluster Variables, 1922/1923; phaedra1201 (Box 50)
  KG11366.199
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1923; phaedra1202 (Box 50)
  KG11366.200
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1922; phaedra1203 (Box 50)
  KG11366.201
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1921/1924; phaedra1204 (Box 50)
  KG11366.202
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1925/1928; phaedra1205 (Box 50)
  KG11366.203
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1924/1925; phaedra1206 (Box 50)
  KG11366.204
- New Variables, 1924/1926; phaedra1207 (Box 50)
  KG11366.205
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1924/1925; phaedra1208 (Box 50)
  KG11366.206
- Cluster Variables, 1927; phaedra1209 (Box 50)
  KG11366.207
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1925; phaedra1210 (Box 50)
  KG11366.208
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1902/1904; phaedra1211 (Box 50)
  KG11366.209
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, MC and MF Plates, 1926/1930; phaedra1212 (Box 50)
  KG11366.210
- Interesting Objects, Suspected Variables, 1926; phaedra1213 (Box 50)
  KG11366.211
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; phaedra1214 (Box 50)
  KG11366.212
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; phaedra1215 (Box 50)
  KG11366.213
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; phaedra1216 (Box 50)
  KG11366.214
- New Variables, 1926; phaedra1217 (Box 50)
  KG11366.215
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1927/1928; phaedra1218 (Box 50)
  KG11366.216
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1926; phaedra1219 (Box 51)
  KG11366.217
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1926; phaedra1220 (Box 51)
  KG11366.218
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1926; phaedra1221 (Box 51)
  KG11366.219
- Cluster Variables, 1927; phaedra1222 (Box 51)
  KG11366.220
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1929; phaedra1223 (Box 51)
  KG11366.221
- Dr. Gerasimonic, T Pyx, Shapley LPV's, 1927; phaedra1224 (Box 51)
  KG11366.222
- Spectrophotometry, Schilt Measures, 1931; phaedra1225 (Box 51)
  KG11366.223
  G. Maulbetsch
- Spectrophotometry, Schilt Measures, 1931; phaedra1226 (Box 51)